# Aldzikri Dwijayanto Prathama

🛮 +6285641486513 | 💌 aldzikridp@gmail.com | 🖸 aldzikridp | 🛅 aldzikridp

# Personal Profile

I am a graduate of Bachelor's Degree in Informatics, and have been a Linux and BSD user since 2016 as well as a self-hosting enthusiast. I am interested in network infrastructure and server administration. In addition, I am also a fan of programming in C, container technologies, virtualization, and reproducibility.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

PT Pundi Mas Berjaya Batam, Indonesia

Server Management

Agustus 2022 - Desember 2022

- Hardware & Software server maintenance
- · Monitoring & Logging server
- · Monitoring & Logging network
- Troubleshooting
- Setting-up email server
- Managing DNS
- Deploying container & virtual machine
- · Designing Network

#### **Dinas Kesehatan Prov. DIY**

Web Admin

- Juli 2022 Agustus 2022 • Deploying & Managing Web
- · Giving advice for web design

**PT Presentologics** Dicoding Kampus Merdeka, Front End Web & Back End Developer

Bandung, Indonesia

Agustus 2021 - Januari 2022

Yogyakarta, Indonesia

- AWS Cloud Training
- Developing Javascript Web Apps
- Deploying Javascript Web Apps

#### Skills

**Programming** C, Bash, Java, Javascript, Latex, Lua, Nix, PHP, SQL

Centos, Alma linux, Debian, Ubuntu, NixOS, Proxmox, Fedora **Operating System** 

Server & Network GNS3, firewalld, UFW, iDRAC, Systemd, MySQL, MariaDB, Nginx, Apache, Docker, Podman, Qemu, Wireguard, OpenVPN

Miscellaneous Git, Vim/Neovim

## Education

## Universitas Teknologi Digital Indonesia

Yogyakarta, Indonesia

2019 - 2023

Strata 1 Jurusan Informatika • GPA 3.72/4.00

• Terpilih mengikuti program Kampus Merdeka Angkatan 1, dan Angkatan 3

# Certificate

#### **Adinusa**

· Linux System Administration

### PT Pundi Mas Berjaya

· Server Management

#### **Dicoding**

- Cloud Practitioner Essentials (AWS Cloud)
- Menjadi Front-End Web Developer Expert
- Belajar Dasar-Dasar DevOps
- Memulai Pemrograman Dengan C
- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula